Guide to the The George Washington University Bulletin records, 1821-2011 RG0127
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
The George Washington University Bulletin
1821-2021
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
RG0127
36 Linear Feet
Collection contains the bulletins of The George Washington University, from all schools and colleges. These bulletins include special addresses, reports, and pictorial bulletins, as well as academic courses, fees, and degree requirements.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from Office of Admissions.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains the bulletins of The George Washington University, from all schools and colleges. These bulletins include special addresses, reports, and pictorial bulletins. These items date from 1821 to the present day. The bulletins provide history of GW including listing faculty, degrees conferred, course taught, and information related to student life.
Additional information within the bulletins includes addresses by university faculty, alumni, administrators, and speakers at convocations; government documents concerning the university, student society publications, and some issues of treasurers' and comptrollers'reports (1876-1944). Also includes other schools within the university, as well as some summaries of dissertations.
This collection contains copies of the bulletins produced by The George Washington University from all schools and colleges. These volumes include special addresses, reports, and pictorial bulletins. The material dates from 1821 to the present.
Existence and Location of Originals
The GW Bulletins from 2006 to Present are also available on the GW Bulletin website - http://bulletin.gwu.edu/archives/
Policies and institutions; Thesis and dissertations; Students; Buildings; Commencement ceremonies -- Washington (D.C.); Reports and studies; Research; Scholarships; Faculty; Presidents; Conferences; Dormitories; Clubs; Awards; Washington (D.C.); George Washington University--History; George Washington University. Board of Trustees; George Washington University; George Washington University--Alumni and alumnae
- Bulletins, 1875-2021; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Box numbers start with Box 12.
  General
  Note that box 39 also contains the bulletins for the School of Medicine for 1959-1972.
  The GW Bulletin has been published digitally since 2006.
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1875-1903; Series 1 (Box 12)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1902-1905; Series 1 (Box 13)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1906-1910; Series 1 (Box 14)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1910-1916; Series 1 (Box 15)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1916-1922; Series 1 (Box 16)
    Please note this box does not contain the 1919 yearbook. The only copy is in the Reading Room.
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1922-1930; Series 1 (Box 17)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1931-1934; Series 1 (Box 18)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1933-1938; Series 1 (Box 19)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1938-1942; Series 1 (Box 20)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1942-1947; Series 1 (Box 21)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1947-1951; Series 1 (Box 22)
  - Catalogues, 1950-1954; Series 1 (Box 23)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1954-1958; Series 1 (Box 24)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1957-1961; Series 1 (Box 25)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1961-1965; Series 1 (Box 26)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1964-1968; Series 1 (Box 27)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1967-1971; Series 1 (Box 28)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1970-1937; Series 1 (Box 29)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1972-1975; Series 1 (Box 30)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1975-1977; Series 1 (Box 31)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1978-1980; Series 1 (Box 32)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1979-1982; Series 1 (Box 33)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1982-1986; Series 1 (Box 34)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 35)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 36)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1991-1997; Series 1 (Box 37)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 1997-2005; Series 1 (Box 38)
  - Bulletins and catalogues, 2005-2007; Series 1 (Box 39)
  - Digital Bulletins, 2006-2021
    Scope and Contents
    The GW Bulletins have been online since the mid-2000s. In addition to our files, they are also posted on the GW Bulletin website: http://bulletin.gwu.edu/archives/